leadcapturepagesystem.com 2016-10-13

# Disclosure/Privacy Policy

_Last Updated on June 11, 2013_

## Overview

Welcome to LeadCapturePageSystem.com.  Throughout this privacy policy we will refer to LeadCapturePageSystem.com and the other websites that Lead Capture Page System owns as "LCPS".  We've put together this Privacy Policy to describe our collection, use and disclosure of information from users of our software, our websites and any other services we offer.  When using any of our products or services you consent to the collection, disclosure and other uses of your information as described below.  We're constantly improving things at LCPS, and our Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time.  If we make important changes to the Privacy Policy we will provide advance notice of those changes through our newsletter.

## Information Collected

  * **Registration Information.**    If you sign up for a LCPS Account, we ask you to provide us with personal information, such as your name, username, password, photo and email address.  We may also ask you to personalize your user experience with other information such as your location, and your individual preferences.  This information collectively is referred to as "Registration Information."  Some of this information, for example, your name and username, will be listed publicly on our Services, including in search results.
  * **IDs.**   When you register at a LCPS website we create a unique id number associated with the registration.  This unique id number is used to identify your account and is shared between sites owned by LCPS.
  * **Log Data.**   When you use our website or services we record information about your use ("Log Data").  This Log Data may include information such as your computer's or mobile device's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, the webpage you were visiting before you came to our site, pages of our site that you visit, access times and dates and other statistics.
  * **Usage Information.**   We also collect information about how you use our website and services, including how you view and interact with content and advertisements, the parts of our services that you use, information you search for, content that you view, and actions you take such as asking questions, visiting pages or posting comments.
  * **Surveys and Promotions.**   From time to time, we may provide you the opportunity to participate in surveys, contests or sweepstakes via our Services.  If you participate, we may request certain additional information from you.

## How Information Collected is Used

  * We use information we collect, including your Registration Information, ID, information from your use of our services and information from surveys and promotions to improve our services, develop new services and offers and enhance and personalize your experience on LCPS, including the content and advertising that you see.
  * We may use your Registration Information to send you important messages regarding the services, as well as marketing materials that we think may be of interest to you.  If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive marketing communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in those communications.

## Disclosure of the Information Collected

  * **Information You Share.**   In some cases, the actions you take on the Services, will be viewable by other users.  For example, positive feedback you leave is dynamically posted on our testimonials page as an anonymous testimonial. Also, we may list websites or designs we create for you in our portfolio.  When listing your site in our portfolio we may show details about your site such as it's domain name, amount of members, date added, and version of software used.  We make our best effort to protect your privacy and confidentiality of your business and only share details that are either already public knowledge or that we believe is not confidential and acceptable to be shared. If you need to update your personal information that we have stored you can either log into your account and modify it yourself OR you can email support@leadcapturepagesystem.com
  * **With Your Consent.**   We may disclose any information we collect with third parties when we receive your consent to do so.
  * **Non-Private or Non-Personal Information.**   We may disclose aggregated and non-personally identifiable information that we collect.  Any such disclosure will not include non-public, personal information regarding individual users.
  * **Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement.**   LCPS cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of LCPS or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person or to prevent or restrict what we consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.
  * **Services Providers.**   We may employ third parties to assist us in providing and improving the products and services we offer.  If these third parties receive non-public, personal information about you, they will be obligated not to disclose or use it for any purpose other than to perform tasks on our behalf.
  * **Business Transfers.**   LCPS may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including the information identified in this Privacy Policy, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.

## Sharing System Data with 3rd Parties

LCPS will not share your system data with 3rd parties outside of compliance with laws and law enforcement.

## Cookies & Other Technologies

Our services may use "cookies" to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes.  We may use "persistent cookies" to save your email for future logins.  We also may use "session ID cookies" to track temporary information about you on our server. You can instruct your web browser to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting certain or all cookies.  If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all aspects of our website.

Cookies placed on your device or computer by LCPS or any third party site or service that you may access through the Services may remain stored on your device or computer until you remove them.

We work with third-party companies that use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect non-identifying information about your activities on our site in order to help us better understand the use and operation of our site. These third parties collect and analyze information about your activities on our websites and services.

## Information Security

LCPS employs reasonable physical, technological and administrative security measures to protect the information it collects.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, while we use commercially acceptable means to protect the information we collect, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If LCPS learns of a security breach that results in the unauthorized disclosure of your Registration Information, we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps.  LCPS may also send an e-mail to you at the e-mail address you have provided to us for a notification pursuant to this paragraph.

## Phishing

Identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to LCPS.  Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority.  We do not and will not request your credit card information, your account ID, login password or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication.

## International Transfer

If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, LCPS transfers that information, including personal information about you, to the United States and processes it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy and provision of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

## Links to Other Sites

Our websites contains links to other websites and online services.  If you choose to visit a third party service or an advertiser by "clicking on" a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's website or online service.  The fact that we link to a website, content or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices.  Other websites and services follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them.  We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites and services you use.  We do not exercise control over third party websites or services. 

## Contact Information

You can contact us be email at sales@leadcapturepagesystem.com. You can contact us by phone at 1-888-65LEADS. You may send us mail at: 102 Thompson Dr, Bridgeport, WV 26330. [For more information about contacting us click here](http://leadcapturepagesystem.com/contactus.php).
